You and I are two lost souls in sheets.
I'm alive that I can barely breathe.
With your arms around me, I feel like I'm drowning.
If I reach for something I can't keep.
How
I could really deep.
So baby, let's get messy, let's get all the way undone.
Come over and just taste just like I've never been touched.
Baby, I've since with you and there's no replica.
Maybe if it's messy, if it's messy, if it's messy, then you know it's really love.
I want
All of your complicated.
Give me all of your words.
When the party's over and I'm screaming I hate it, how bad could it really hurt?
If tonight we just let it burn.
So baby, let's get nasty, let's get all the way undone.
Cover just
say I've never been touched.
Baby, I'm obsessed with you and there's a replica.
Baby, if it's a see, if it's a see, if it's a see, then you know it's really.
Oh.
You're pulling back and I'm running for the door, you.
Saying those.
words and it just makes me want you more.
A second chance with a heart on the floor.
This is oh.
So baby, let's get this thing, let's get all the way undressed.
Come over and touch me just like I've never been touched.
Baby, I'm obsessed with you and there's a replica.
Even if it's messy, if it's
I see
this is the sea and you know it's really low.
Oh.
Yeah, you know it's really low.