Crayon Shin-chan
machi no doubutsuen wa isogashii
The town zoo is a busy place
taihen da sorya taihen da
It's a nightmare, a total nightmare
watashi mo chotto taihen na no yo
I'm also somewhat a nightmare
aitsu no haato oikakete
As I chase after her heart
natsu no hizashi wa koi no rizumu na no ni
If sunshine is the rhythm of love,
doushite na no hitori ja odorenai
Why can't I dance alone?
natsu no doubutsuen wa isogashii
The summer zoo is a busy place
zou-san kazehiki
The elephant caught a cold
hana mizu no shawaa dazou
Creating a snot shower
kuma-san tetsuya de
The bears were able
me ni kuma ga dekita
To see everything during the night
taihen da sorya taihen da
It's a nightmare, a total nightmare
Running
an Errand
Running an errand!
Nohara
Hiroshi
Misae
Shinnosuke
Oh no! I forgot to buy the ground pork and radishes!
Now I've done it.
We're out of soy sauce too!
Shoot! And I have my hands full at the moment.
What should I do?
Oh, I know!
I'll get Shinnosuke to go for me.
He's never gone shopping by himself before,
so it'll be a good
experience for him.
Shinnosuke!
What?
Can you come here for a sec?
I can't right now. I'm drawing!
What a defiant brat. I suppose I'll have to soft-soap him.
Did it turn out nice?
Yeah!
I want to see it!
Sure!
Check it out. It's an elephant!
An elephant, an elephant...
He's such a fool.
I don't have time for this!
And Mom... and Dad...
Listen to me!
Put on some underwear!
I put on some underwear. What did you want?
Go shopping for me.
Do it yourself, Misae.
How many times have I told you not to imitate your father?
I know, Misae.
Don't call your
parents by their names.
Yes, ma'am.
Tonight, your father is bringing home a very important client,
so I'm making a special dinner.
I see.
That's why I'm so busy.
And I want you to help me out.
Will you go shopping for me?
Yeah, no problem!
Wait a minute!
Do you even know what to get?
Potato chips and a Okamoto Natsuki photo spread!
No!!
Listen closely. We need ground pork and radishes...
H-Hold on a second.
I need to take a mome.
You mean "memo," not "mome." I guess he is still just a kid.
Um...
Huh? You're left-handed?
Oh! It was this hand!
Come on now...
First, ground pork.
Ground...
What letter does "ground" start with?
It's okay.
I'll write the list.
Radishes... Soy sauce...
What is it?
Your writing looks like a worm.
• Ground pork
• Radishes
• Soy sauce
Thanks for helping out, Shin-chan!
Hello!
Welcome!
Running an errand?
What a big boy!
May I have some
ground pork please?
We don't sell pork here.
May I have some radishes then?
We don't sell radish here either.
May I have some soy sauce then?
We don't sell soy sauce either.
Fresh Fish      Koi
This place has a terrible selection.
What are you talking about? We're a fish market!
Fresh Fish      Koi
Welcome!
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
May I have some
ground pork please?
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
m 0 0 l 151 0 151 150 0 150
Meat
Butcher
Of course!
How much do you want?
Uh, may I have two or three?
Didn't you mother tell you how many grams?
How many grams...
Oh!
You remembered?
So how many grams?
She didn't tell me.
This isn't going to work out...
Why don't we call your house and ask your mom?
Okay.
What's your telephone number?
Everything's all set.
All that's left is the radishes and ground pork.
Welcome home!
It's "I'm home,"
not "welcome home."
Wh-What's wrong?
What's our phone number?
O-Our phone number?
Shinnosuke, I'm going to do the shopping.
Watch over house while I'm gone.
You should've just
gone to begin with.
I don't want to hear it!
Don't touch the food I prepared for the important client!
Mom!
If some guy you don't know comes up to you, don't go with him.
Shut! Your! Mouth!
Help me! Help me!
Quiet! No one's going turtle come save you!
You're wrong! I know that Action Kamen will come and save me!
Turtle, turtle, turtle!
Action Kamen? Too bad I, Black Turtle, already took care of him.
Who's there?!
They call me...
Action Mask!
Action Kick!
Action Beam!
Turtle!
Thank you, Action Kamen!
I'm home.
Action Beam!
Are you done?
Yeah.
Wow, this looks delicious!
Hey, where's Mommy at?
She left us...
What?!
...to get some pork.
Oh, she went shopping.
Hey, Mom's gonna
whip your behind!
Oh, don't worry. My client had to cancel the dinner.
So there's no reason to wait. Let's go ahead and eat.
Okay.
Isn't this tasty, Shinnosuke?
Yeah, it is.
So what did you do today, Shinnosuke?
I went shopping.
Wow, you're so grown up!
I am so grown up!
Wait for me!
Darling! Shin-chan!
Oh
●
Oh!
Mommy's Mornings Are Busy
Mommy's mornings are busy!
He's only ridden the kindergarten bus three days this month,
even though this month has already been paid for.
Such a waste.
Shinnosuke! It's morning!
How long are
you going to sleep for?
Come on, get up.
You're going to be late again.
What are we going to do if you don't get on the bus?
Hey, Shinnosuke!
All right then...
Hey, get up!
Huh?
Shinnosuke's disappeared!
Could he have been spirited away?
You're not supposed to sleep in there, Shinnosuke!
I'm sleepy.
Of course you are.
You should've gone to bed earlier.
I knew that you wouldn't be able to get up when you stayed up that late.
It's your own fault.
You're crushing me.
Hey, don't sleep in there!
C'mon, get your clothes out yourself and change into them.
Okay.
Hurry up and change.
Don't tell me...
No more sleeping!
Yeah, just like that.
Hurry up now.
Underwear... Underwear...
Pants... Pants...
That's not right.
All done.
After getting dressed, make sure everything's in your bag.
Okay.
Monthly Ikagawa
It's in here.
Why are you taking
something like that?!
That doesn't need to be in there!
Okay, pack your tissues and handkerchief.
Done.
Hey, hold on!
This isn't a handkerchief!
Here, wash your face with some cold water. It'll wake you up.
Quickly wash up.
Okay...
I've got a bad feeling...
I knew it!
Feel the wrath of my triple punch of anger!
Eat your breakfast.
It's not beef stew?
That takes too long to make for the morning.
Just hurry up and eat.
Midori from the kindergarten tells me to eat slowly.
Call her "Yoshinaga-sensei"!
Chew well and
quickly eat your food.
If you would have
gotten up earlier,
you could've eaten your breakfast more slowly.
I'm finished.
But you haven't even started.
You changed the soup, didn't you?
Never mind that. Hurry up!
I'll eat this.
These are no ordinary bean.
They are just normal beans.
Did you steal them?
Why would you think I stole them?!
Then you bought them?
Of course I did!
Then they aren't just normal beans.
Just hurry up and eat!
I'm an idiot for giving him beans.
You look depressed, Misae.
Hurry up!
Did you brush your teeth?
I did.
Did you go pee?
Did you poop?
I didn't.
Hurry up now.
The bus is here to pick you up.
Oh, I don't have my hat...
Hurry and go get it!
Here.
If you don't make it
on the bus today,
it won't be the only
thing leaving you.
I couldn't find it, so I'll use this.
You idiot!
Good morning, sensei!
Good morning!
Good afternoon!
You mean "good morning."
Okay, Shin-chan.
Why don't you get on the bus?
Okay, whatever you say, Midori.
What's wrong, Shinnosuke?
I need to poop.
Just keep it in!
A bit came out...
Go on without him.
I'll bring him in later.
Okay...
The bus fare...
The morning sun is radiant.
Shinnosuke had to poop, so we were late once again.
Ooh
▲
Ooh!
Doodling
Doodling!
Good morning, sensei!
Good morning!
Today, we're going to doodle.
Did everyone bring their crayons?
Yes!
Okay, then...
Shinnosuke-kun?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I've got a nosebleed.
If you keep doing that, you're going to have nose like a pig!
Have you tried this, sensei?
Does it look like I have a pig nose?
Calm down, Midori. You shouldn't get so worked up over a kid.
Shin-chan! This is the second time I've told you to stop playing around.
I've got a runny nose.
I told you to stop!
Today, you can draw whatever you like.
Animals, flowers — anything is fine!
Okay!
What are you going to draw, Shin-chan?
Where are you going, Shin-chan?
You want me to stay still?
Hey, what are you
doing over there?
Drawing what I like.
You don't need to use a model.
A drawing is something you use your imagination to come up with on paper.
My imagination?
Yes! You close your eyes like this and draw whatever you see in your head.
Wow! I can see a beautiful flower garden!
Now you give it a try!
Yeah, just like that.
Oh!
Good! Now do you see anything?
I can't see anything except darkness.
Okay, let's see what kind of things you are all drawing!
You're drawing a flower, right, Nene-chan?
That's right, Yoshinaga-sensei!
It's a beautiful flower.
I really tried hard to draw it.
Me too, sensei.
I'm a beautiful flower.
Quit with your nonsense.
Nonsense?
Stop sticking crayons up your nose!
Okay.
Masao-kun, what are you drawing?
Let me see it.
I-I'm not done with it yet.
That's fine!
Let me just take a peek then.
No. It's terrible!
I'm sure it's fine.
No! It's really bad!
I see...
It really is bad.
I'm sorry, Masao-kun!
I shouldn't have done that.
You made him cry.
Hey now, I wasn't
the one who did it.
Bo-chan?
Can I see your drawing?
Sure.
Bo-chan, what is
this supposed to be?
Is it the sun?
A ball.
O-Of course, it's a ball!
Nicely done.
Even I could draw
something like that.
There's no point if you're just copying others.
Kazama-kun!
Hey, Yoshinaga-sensei!
So what did you draw?
I'm not really confident in it.
Wow, you're very talented, Kazama-kun.
I personally don't think I got the color of the sky quite right though.
Let me see it too.
Hehe, he can see it.
It's not like seeing it will make his any better.
What do you think of my skills?
What is it?
What's wrong with it?
There's no heart in this drawing.
What?!
Are you nitpicking my drawing?!
No, there's just no heart in it.
I'll add some in.
Could I have been the one to discover Shin-chan's artistic talent?
That's great, Shin-chan!
Try to put some heart into it!
All done.
Shinnosuke
How could you do this to my masterpiece?
I'm sorry, Kazama-kun!
You made someone else cry!
It's all your fault!
Do you understand, Shin-chan?
Without bothering anyone else,
draw your own picture by yourself.
Okay.
Really try.
Looks good.
You haven't even
drawn anything yet.
But I thought I could whatever.
Anything is fine.
Like an airplane or a bicycle.
I'll draw an airplane!
What's wrong, Shin-chan?
What does an
airplane look like again?
Like this! In the middle, you have the body that looks like a log...
I see...
Then it has two big wings and three small ones.
And then it flies!
Varooom! Varooom!
Woooosh! Woooosh!
Did you get that?
Yes!
What does it look like again?
Forget it.
I'll help you out a bit.
Thanks!
Nene
Nene-chan.
Bo
Bo-chan.
Kazama
Kazama-kun.
And...
Shinnosuke
Shin-chan.
Even for a kid from the Sunflower Class,
he drew a good kindergartner-like drawing, didn't he?
Matsuzaka-sensei!
But that's not even the average level for my Rose Class.
Only in your class would that be considered excellent.
I can't let her know that I actually drew most of it.
Like this, okay?
I see...
And then like this...
All done!
Huh? Where'd Shinnosuke go?
Look, he's in there.
Well, look at that.
Apparently, he was so into drawing today
that he tired himself out.
See ya
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
See ya!
uta wo utaou kimi no tame ni
Let's sing a song for you
shiawase de arimasu you ni
So that you can be happy
uta wo utaou kimi no tame ni
Let's sing a song for you
shiawase de arimasu you ni
So that you can be happy
kokoro kara utau
Sing it from your heart
uta wo utaou kimi no tame ni
Let's sing a song for you
shiawase de arimasu you ni
So that you can be happy
uta wo utaou kimi no tame ni
Let's sing a song for you
shiawase de arimasu you ni
So that you can be happy
kokoro kara utau
Sing it from your heart