Words: the, nightmare, taihen, busy, doubutsuen
Phrase: Crayon Shin-chan
Phrase: machi no doubutsuen wa isogashii
Words: and, what, you, for, ground
Phrase: Nohara
Phrase: Hiroshi
Misae
Shinnosuke
Words: chan, for, helping, out, shin
Phrase: Thanks for helping out, Shin-chan!
Words: fish, fresh, koi, butcher, meat
Phrase: Hello!
Phrase: Welcome!
Words: home, all, welcome, and, everything's
Phrase: Everything's all set.
Phrase: All that's left is the radishes and ground pork.
Words: don't, the, you, gone, i'm
Phrase: Wh-What's wrong?
Phrase: What's our phone number?
Words: action, turtle, kamen, come, help
Phrase: Help me! Help me!
Phrase: Quiet! No one's going turtle come save you!
Words: action, beam, home, i'm
Phrase: I'm home.
Phrase: Action Beam!
Words: grown, hey, she, shinnosuke, shopping
Phrase: Are you done?
Phrase: Yeah.
Words: are, busy, mommy's, mornings, chan
Phrase: Wait for me!
Darling! Shin-chan!
Phrase: Oh
Words: going, are, bus, for, get
Phrase: He's only ridden the kindergarten bus three days this month,
Phrase: even though this month has already been paid for.
Words: all, right, then
Phrase: All right then...
Words: away, been, could, disappeared, get
Phrase: Hey, get up!
Phrase: Huh?
Words: you, that, you're, able, are
Phrase: You're not supposed to sleep in there, Shinnosuke!
Phrase: I'm sleepy.
Words: and, change, c'mon, clothes, don't
Phrase: Hey, don't sleep in there!
Phrase: C'mon, get your clothes out yourself and change into them.
Words: underwear, don't, hurry, just, like
Phrase: Don't tell me...
Phrase: No more sleeping!
Words: pants, after, all, bag, done
Phrase: Pants... Pants...
Phrase: That's not right.
Words: ikagawa, monthly, that, and, are
Phrase: Monthly Ikagawa
Words: wash, cold, done, face, handkerchief
Phrase: Done.
Phrase: Hey, hold on!
Words: bad, feeling, got, i've
Phrase: I've got a bad feeling...
Words: anger, feel, knew, punch, the
Phrase: I knew it!
Phrase: Feel the wrath of my triple punch of anger!
Words: eat, you, your, and, breakfast
Phrase: Eat your breakfast.
Phrase: It's not beef stew?
Words: you, changed, didn't, hurry, mind
Phrase: You changed the soup, didn't you?
Phrase: Never mind that. Hurry up!
Words: just, them, you, are, beans
Phrase: I'll eat this.
Phrase: These are no ordinary bean.
Words: you, did, hurry, the, bus
Phrase: I'm an idiot for giving him beans.
Phrase: You look depressed, Misae.
Words: good, morning, you, okay, afternoon
Phrase: Good morning, sensei!
Phrase: Good morning!
Words: just, keep, need, poop, shinnosuke
Phrase: What's wrong, Shinnosuke?
Phrase: I need to poop.
Words: him, bit, bring, came, i'll
Phrase: A bit came out...
Phrase: Go on without him.
Words: the, again, bus, fare, had
Phrase: The bus fare...
Phrase: The morning sun is radiant.
Words: ooh, doodling, good, morning, bring
Phrase: Ooh
Phrase: ▲
Words: you, have, i've, like, nose
Phrase: Shinnosuke-kun?
Phrase: What's wrong? Are you okay?
Words: you, draw, animals, anything, are
Phrase: I've got a runny nose.
Phrase: I told you to stop!
Words: you, see, like, your, anything
Phrase: Where are you going, Shin-chan?
Phrase: You want me to stay still?
Words: drawing, i'm, it's, see, flower
Phrase: Okay, let's see what kind of things you are all drawing!
Phrase: You're drawing a flower, right, Nene-chan?
Words: ball, draw, what, chan, confident
Phrase: Bo-chan, what is
this supposed to be?
Phrase: Is it the sun?
Words: see, the, think, any, better
Phrase: Wow, you're very talented, Kazama-kun.
Phrase: Let me see it too.
Words: what
Phrase: What is it?
Words: shinnosuke, you, heart, shin, all
Phrase: What's wrong with it?
Phrase: There's no heart in this drawing.
Words: really, try
Phrase: Really try.
Words: airplane, anything, bicycle, but, could
Phrase: Looks good.
Phrase: You haven't even
drawn anything yet.
Words: like, and, see, that, the
Phrase: What's wrong, Shin-chan?
Phrase: What does an
airplane look like again?
Words: again, bit, does, forget, help
Phrase: What does it look like again?
Phrase: Forget it.
I'll help you out a bit.
Words: nene, chan, class, even, for
Phrase: Nene
Words: like, this, actually, all, and
Phrase: I can't let her know that I actually drew most of it.
Phrase: Like this, okay?
Words: look, that, apparently, drawing, he's
Phrase: Huh? Where'd Shinnosuke go?
Phrase: Look, he's in there.
Words: see
Phrase: See ya
Words: you, sing, arimasu, can, for
Phrase: uta wo utaou kimi no tame ni
Phrase: Let's sing a song for you